We have some time
before your appointment
with the principal.
Do you want to stop anywhere?
No thanks, I'll surprise him
and show up early for a change.
Stop here.
[Kiyotaka] Huh?
Right here?
[Satoru] You go on ahead.
(grunts in surprise)
[Kiyotaka] Is this a
test or something?
You're going to hit
me if I drive away
without you, aren't you?
[Satoru] Just what type
of guy do you think I am?
(sighs in relief)
-[Kiyotaka] Okay then.
-(tires screeching)
All right.
(shrieks)
(ground breaking)
I see.
Who are you, then?
(yells battle cry)
(fire roaring)
(chuckles)
That was a whole lot easier
than I expected it was gonna be.
Huh?
[Satoru] So then.
Just who are you calling "easy"?
(groans)
What a pain in the ass.
He's a cursed spirit, but
he can communicate clearly.
And the sheer amount of
cursed energy he just unleashed.
An unregistered special-grade?
He's likely even stronger
than Sukuna currently is.
Special-grades are
classified as such
because they're special.
Having them pop
up this frequently
throws everything off.
(laughs mockingly)
Aw, don't tell me I
wounded your pride?
No.
(knuckles cracking)
I'm starting to enjoy this.
(chuckles)
(Opening Theme Music)
(singing in Japanese)
[Jougo] So you think
this will be fun, do you?
No sense of danger?
None at all?
Did he choose to attack
here in order to avoid people?
No.
He was just making
sure no other sorcerers
could come to back me up.
Ember Insects!
Well, if you're aiming
this attack at me,
then you're right.
I'm not feeling any danger.
(ground breaking)
Well!
What if this hits me?
(insect chattering)
Sound?
(insects exploding)
A two-stage attack of
sound and explosions?
That's not bad.
(yells battle cry)
(fire roaring)
And there's more!
(ground breaking)
(fire exploding)
That's all it took?
Obviously, I overestimated him.
That human was just as
fragile as the rest of them are.
He wasn't living
any life of truth.
It's all so
nauseatingly repulsive!
I am going to go and
spread real strength.
The truth as only
death can reveal it!
(Satoru sighs) We just
went over this a minute ago.
Are you a slow learner?
(coughs) This
smoke is so irritating.
What's going on here?
(hums)
In simple terms, you missed me.
Impossible, I felt
the contact just now!
I touched you, and not
only that, I killed you!
No, what you actually touched
was the "Infinity" existing
between you and me.
Here, I'll show you.
Put your hand out.
(grumbles)
Oh, come on!
Come on, come on!
I don't sense
hostility or trickery.
Guess I'll see what it's about.
(gasps)
See?
I can't touch him!
I get stopped just short of him!
Is this Infinity?
Not exactly stopped,
but the closer you
get, the slower you go.
(groans)
So, what now?
We could just hold
hands if you like.
I refuse!
Oh, don't be shy now.
You're making me
feel self-conscious, too!
(growls)
You bastard!
-(punch landing)
-(groans in pain)
(coughs wetly)
So fast!
I don't get it, it's
not just a blow
that's strengthened
with cursed energy!
So, what is it?
I must know!
There's still more!
-(punches landing)
-(grunting in pain)
(screams)
Infinity exists everywhere.
I just use my jujutsu to
bring it forward into reality.
Convergence, divergence.
What do you think happens
when one touches this void?
Cursed Technique Reversal.
Red.
(grunts)
(ground breaking)
-(grunting)
-(trees snapping)
-(yells)
-(punch landing)
-(body thudding)
-(grunting in pain)
(grunting in pain)
(yells battle cry)
-(kick landing)
-(screams)
(body slamming)
Well, that's that.
(rain falling)
[Sugeru] You can try,
but you'll die.
Jougo.
(water splashing)
I guess it wasn't just talk.
(chuckles)
No matter.
If I can't hit him, I'll just
drag him into my Domain.
Wait.
Where'd he go?
Sorry about that.
-Huh?
-Hey, what's going on here?
Where in the hell are
we? How did I get here?
-Sorry.
-I don't get it!
What is this place, hey!
What the hell?
Sukuna's vessel?
To observe, I've
brought Yuuji Itadori.
Mount Fuji!
His head's Mount Fuji!
(footsteps tapping)
I aim to protect you!
I'll never leave you!
-(snoring)
-[Frodo] Sam.
(Sam sobbing)
Wow.
He learns surprisingly quickly.
-[Frodo] Come on, Sam.
-[Satoru] Yuuji!
(yelps)
Oh hey, so what's up, Gojou?
Talking to him doesn't
cause a problem, either.
You need something?
[Satoru] So we can
increase his output quickly
and move on to
the next stage soon.
We're heading out, let's go.
Huh?
[Satoru] It's a
field trip lesson.
I'm going to teach you
about the very pinnacle
of jujutsu battles.
Domain Expansion.
(water splashing)
What the hell's this?
How come I'm not sinking?
Gojou, I was at the school
just 10 seconds ago, right?
What's going on, here?
Oh, I warped us.
He's not gonna explain it.
Sukuna's vessel!
So he really is alive.
[Suguru] The first thing,
you must somehow render
Satoru Gojou incapable of fighting.
The second is to get Ryoumen
Sukuna and Yuuji Itadori
on your side.
I can't kill Itadori because
of our future plans.
Has Gojou figured
out what we're up to?
What'd you bring
the kid for, a shield?
A shield?
No, no, I already
explained this.
He's just here to watch.
You see, I'm in the midst of
teaching him a lot of things.
So forget about him
and let's just fight.
Having him tag along with
you isn't gonna slow you down?
It makes you look like an idiot.
Oh, no, it'll all be fine.
I mean, really.
You're kind of weak.
(chuckles)
(growls)
(fire roaring)
How dare you insult me
like that, you insolent ass?
I'm going to enjoy tearing
up that smug face of yours!
(fire exploding)
(water crashing)
This guy
is weak?
He's way more powerful
than any of the monsters
I've encountered so far!
(shudders)
(grunts)
You'll be fine.
Just stay here close to me.
(grunts)
Domain Expansion!
(gasps)
(ground breaking)
(lava bubbling)
(chuckles)
What is this?
Damn!
Coffin of the Iron Mountain!
(lava bubbling)
(lava exploding)
What is this?
Damn!
[Satoru] This is
Domain Expansion.
(chuckles evilly)
The Innate Domain is made
-with cursed energy.
-(yelps)
Then, you imbue it
with a cursed technique.
(blows air rapidly)
What you three encountered
at that juvenile detention center
was an incomplete
Domain that hadn't been
imbued with any
cursed techniques.
If that had been
a proper Domain,
all of you first-years
would have died.
I think Megumi understood that.
Spreading out an
Innate Domain that way
always consumes a ton of energy.
But the advantages
make it worth it.
One of them is
the boost to stats
due to environmental factors.
Ah!
You mean like
buffs in video games!
Another one is...
(rock exploding)
What?
Most sorcerers would
have been burned to ash
the moment they
entered my Domain!
The techniques
imbued in the Domain
are always sure to
hit within that Domain.
That is guaranteed.
Guaranteed?
That's correct!
But don't worry.
There are several
ways to deal with it.
You can take the hit
using a cursed technique,
like just now, or, and I don't
really recommend this one,
but you can try to go
outside the Domain.
That's usually impossible.
Now, you can also-
[Jougo] If I neutralize
that Infinity of yours
with a dense Domain, then
my techniques will reach you.
Yeah, they'll hit.
Infinity?
You have to give
me the Prison Realm!
To add to my collection!
I came here half in jest,
thinking I wouldn't really
care if I couldn't kill him.
But now, having this
difference between us
thrust in my face,
having him insult my pride
as a cursed spirit,
ridiculing the new humanity,
this is completely unacceptable!
The most effective way
to deal with a Domain
is to lay out your own Domain.
When two Domains are
laid out at the same time,
the more refined one
will dominate that space.
Though compatibility and the
amount of energy can factor in.
(foot stomping)
There won't even be ashes
left of you, Satoru Gojou!
(ground breaking)
(Jougo grunts)
Domain Expansion.
Infinite Void.
(crickets chirping)
(water splashing)
[Jougo] What just happened?
Can it be that my
Domain was overwhelmed?
I can't see anything.
I can't feel anything!
No!
I can see everything!
I can feel everything!
But the information
is never complete,
so I can't do anything!
This is the inner
world of Limitless.
Perception, contact.
Every act in life is repeated
infinitely, over and over.
(grunts in shock)
Ironic, isn't it?
When granted every
possible thing, you can't use it.
All you can do
is die peacefully.
But I have some things
I still want to ask you,
so for right now, I'm
going to let you off the hook
with just this.
(flesh stretching)
-(flesh ripping)
-(blood splattering)
(glass shattering)
(head clattering)
-(foot stomping)
-Now, then.
Just who instructed
you to come after me?
He really is the
strongest jujutsu sorcerer!
As a living organism,
he's on another level!
[Sugeru] Oh dear.
What now?
Will you rescue him?
I can't let any of the people
from the school see my face,
so I'll be leaving here now.
I trust you to finish this.
If you want to save him,
then go ahead and save him.
Though I don't know, do your
kind have sentimental emotions?
(distorted backwards speech)
(footsteps tapping)
That's quite a statement
for a cursed spirit to make.
You don't seem like
the type to follow orders.
Was something good supposed
to happen if you killed me?
Regardless, you're
going to have to tell me.
Who sent you?
I want a name.
Come on, just tell me already.
(grunts in pain)
Like I'd ever tell
you, you little punk!
What a bad attitude.
And you're so compromised!
(grunts in pain)
Damn you!
If you don't tell
me, I'll exorcise you.
Though I will anyway.
So weird!
Curses are capable
of conversations?
Here, it almost seems normal.
(ground slamming)
-(grunts in shock)
-(gasps)
(flowers rustling)
Aww!
-So pretty!
-Flowers!
(grunts in confusion)
(laughs joyously)
-(grunts)
-(hand slapping)
It's just a curse!
And it's stripping
away my will to fight!
(screams)
Leave me, Gojou!
Go after them, I'll be fine!
(screams)
Wait, forget that, I lied!
I need help!
(blade slicing)
-(fire roaring)
-(grunts in pain)
(hums in admiration)
He got away.
He's good at
hiding his presence.
He's way more impressive
than Volcano Head.
(flowers rustling)
I'm sorry about that.
So now cursed
spirits of that level
-are joining forces?
-But then you're the one
-who brought me here.
-It's getting interesting!
Yuuji!
I want you, as well as
all of your classmates,
to become strong enough
that you can beat that.
Me, beat that?
It's better to have
a concrete goal,
wouldn't you say?
Man, I'm glad I
brought you today!
Is he serious?
I've had no idea what was
going on this whole time!
Now that we've set you a goal,
all that's left is to pursue
it and then attain it.
Let's speed up your schedule.
For the next month, you'll
still be watching movies,
but you'll also be
fighting against me.
Fighting with you?
(groans dejectedly)
Will I still even be alive
after a month of that?
Then it's combat training.
You'll be sent out on
more difficult missions.
The basics and
how to apply them.
And then finally, you can
show off all these new skills
at the Exchange Event!
Wait, teacher!
Yes?
And what's your question?
The Exchange Event is what?
(grunts questioningly)
[Satoru] I didn't tell you?
(growls)
(stammers)
He's late!
(yelps)
(footsteps tapping)
(door creaking)
(door closing)
(water splashing)
[Suguru] Sure is peaceful here.
How's Jougo doing, Getou?
Death's door.
Hanami wants to
save him, though,
so he'll probably be fine.
How irresponsible.
And you're the one
who egged him on.
Heavens, no.
I tried to stop him.
(door creaking)
[Mahito] Speak of the devil.
Jougo, Hanami!
Glad to see you're okay.
How the hell can you
look at me like this
and say I'm okay?
You're lucky that
you got off so easy.
(growls)
(hums mockingly)
Why, you...
[Suguru] Maybe now
at least you understand.
So we'll go about
sealing Satoru Gojou
at the appropriate time,
in the appropriate place,
once we've secured
our advantage over him.
D-Day is October
31st in Shibuya.
Later, I'll have more details.
Good, Mahito?
No objections.
Let's be cunning,
as curses should.
And humans should.
(chuckles)
(Closing Theme Music)
(singing in Japanese)
(playful music)
[Both] One!
Two and!
Three and!
-Four and!
-What the hell are you doing?
We're warming up.
[Both] Six and!
I think I'm warmed up enough.
Me, too.
(hums questioningly)
What exactly are
you warming up for?
-(whistle blowing)
-(grunts)
(screams)
(lively music)
(panting)
Getou, cross!
(screams)
Thanks!
-Shoot!
-(screams)
(grunts in pain)
Mahito, here!
(screams)
Overhead
bicycle kick!
(screams)
(whistle blowing)
I'm gonna kill these
two for this later!
(intense music)